The directories are structured as follows from the perspective of the root folder.
This list includes a few of the dynamic directories that can be created within specific scripts 
(mainly the important ones, the others are only generated in specific cases and are therefore 
not included in this overview). This overview also excludes the virtual environment directory.


+---data
ª   +---FEA
ª       +---All_flats
ª       ª   +---Flat_30mm_mesh
ª       ª   +---New_8
ª       +---genesis_study
ª       +---Mesh_Independence_study_err
ª       ª   +---bdf
ª       ª   +---op2
ª       +---Plate_sims
ª       ª   +---Arbitrary
ª       ª   +---Fixed_end
ª       ª   +---Flat
ª       ª   +---Mesh_study
ª       ª   +---Perferated
ª       ª       +---New folder
ª       +---second_mesh_ind
ª       +---Unsolved

All images and FE data are stored in the 'data' directory. This includes reference and 
deformed images, BDF and OP2 files as well as images generated after optimisation.

The FEA folder contains the FE data files. I manually generated the OP2 files in Nastran 
after setting up simulations in Apex (I could have probably written something to 
automate that process).

The reference images folder stores the reference images used for the study. If a batch analysis 
is conducted then pattern-class-specific subdirectories are generated within the 
reference images folder. You will find my project images in the 'project_reference' 
folder. 

All data generated from analysis of the images (excluding the generation of optimised images)
is stored in the 'results' folder.